Hello friends welcome back our youtube0
market academy so finally ICICI
Lombard has revealed its third quarter results
so the video has a
lot of information for you ahead if we
talk about income then
in the last quarter it was around
5850 crores and last year it was
around 54 crores whereas if we look at it now then it is around
5822 crores that
means quarterly wise there has been an increase of around 0.5 per cent
and on yearly basis then there is a
jump of around 17 per cent so
year on year performance income
growth is strong but quarter on quarter
results have fallen a bit so further
if we talk about the company's expenses then
in the last quarter it was around 5186 crores and
last year it was around
4588 crores
whereas now it has increased to around
5197 crores that
means quarterly wise there is an increase of around 11 crores
in the company's expenses
And yearly, there is a
growth of around Rs 600 to 700 crores
year after year. Year after year, yearly, there is a
growth in the expenses of the company as well, that is,
income and expenses are
seen increasing quarterly and yearly.
So now let's talk about the net profit of the company.
Last quarter, the
profit of the company was around Rs 693 crores and last
year it was around Rs 431 crores,
whereas now it is being seen around Rs 724 crores, that is,
quarterly, there is a growth of around Rs 30 to 35 crores.
Yearly, there is a growth of around Rs 300 to 350 crores in the profit numbers, that is,
overall the profits of the company are
seen increasing quite well this time.
So now let us talk about EPS i.e.
Earnings per Share. Last
quarter it was around Rs 1 and last year it was
around 8.77 paise, whereas now  EPS is seen to be around ₹1.6 paise, so
friends, overall the company's numbers are
looking quite positive this time, the effect of which is that there are
possibilities of seeing much better returns in the stock in the coming time, so
if you liked the video, please
share your comment and do not
forget to subscribe, so we will meet
in the next video with other interesting
videos, thank you and thanks for
watching.